Yeah!
Wow! Luffy is sporting a larger-than-life afro
with a personality to match!
Yeah! Looking sharp, buddy!
That's messed up.
And there goes the bell!
Yeah!
Gop-gop!
Hiss-a!
My arm is fast, but my fist is all slow!
Nine tails in a rush!
Be careful, kid!
I wouldn't touch that one if I were you!
Ah, and that one, too!
Kuh!
Heh-heh-heh!
Can't say I didn't warn you!
Oh no!
That looks bad!
Full Blast Slow Slow Onslaught vs Invulnerable Luffy!
A series of powerful explosions rocks our ship!
Which just so happens to be the battlefield!
The likely cause of some foxy merchandise that just happens to be explosive!
All this cheating just so happens to be pissing me off!
No wonder that jerk's never lost a match!
Luffy, speak to me!
Hey, sit down!
Using his surroundings to his advantage,
our boss slammed Straw Hat head on with a strategically placed cannon attack!
No! He can't lose!
All I can see is smoke!
Was Straw Hat blown to smithereens?
That was a close one!
Indeed! Foxy's Ocelot was-
Shut up! You're annoying!
It's a miracle!
Straw Hat Luffy is alive!
Whoa! He's alive!
There's no way!
He somehow abated the explosive attack at point blank range!
What amazing speed!
The 100 million Barry Rubber Boy is truly a thing of wonder!
That's the power of the frog!
Hurry it up, Luffy!
Fairly, fairly, fairly, fairly
Fiii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii.
Uh oh! It looks like our boss's next attack is already underway!
What good of he plotting this time!?
Fiii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fii-fiii-fiii-fiii-fii-fii-fii-fiii-fiii-fiii-fiii-fiii and
The sneaky foxy lets out an unsettling laugh from behind a thick screen of smoke,
meanwhile Straw Hat stares cluelessly into the abyss!
The suspense is killing me! Where is our boss hiding?!
Is that him?!
Oh, how'd you like that? You had enough?
You got blown up twice as bad as me!
Shut up, I'm fine! See? Look!
You don't look fine at all!
I don't even want you on my crew anymore!
I'd rather just crush you!
Slow, slow me!
Gum, gum, hum!
I'm gonna break your arm so you can't hit me with those dumb bees!
Ah, does this guy want to fight or not?
There you are, gotcha!
Huh, it was just a cutout?
Slow, slow me!
Now what, huh? Which one is the real me?
Which direction will the beam come from?
How should I know? They all look the same!
Just a bunch of split heads with stupid looking haircuts!
Now a stupid looking split head?
That one!
You jerk!
I may be a cheater, but at least I have a heart!
You're in for it now! Look up!
Hm?
Damn it! A trap door!
That's what you get for keeping your head in the clouds!
You're the one who told me to look up in the first place!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
So I did!
Better look down, too!
Hey, what?
Why is the floor moving?
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Fuck! It's Loopy!
He falls in the water. He's done for!
Come on! You can't let the fight ends this way!
You think you can get rid of me that easy?
Close call.
It wouldn't be any fun if Buffs knocked him out right off the bat.
Hey, you there, Straw Hat! And through power!
This ship's a pain in the butt. What gives?
Hey, Split Head, where'd you go?
What have we here?
Straw Hat's narrow escape didn't seem to impress this foxy pin.
You might even say it's laughing at him.
So there you are!
The cabin of the ship is Foxy's playground.
Will Luffy be lured inside?
Hold on, Luffy, it's a trap!
Whatever you do, do not go in that ship!
I'm gonna beat that jerk's brains out!
Straw Hat throws caution to the wind and dashes inside the ship.
Unfortunately, that means I can't give you play-by-play anymore.
But I think it's safe to assume that whatever's going on in there
is completely amazing.
But leave!
It's time to put those wings to the Tesla bird!
So spread them and fly!
These seats are bad enough without you standing in the way.
Cool, a gun deck. It's huge, too.
Too bad Usopp isn't here, he'd love this.
Now, where'd Foxy run off to?
Aha! He's over there!
Fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee.
All right, good. He's coming after me.
And now, he'll come rushing through that door like an idiot.
But we'll see how chipper our little rubber boy is!
Who in my room full of two-foot steel spikes makes Swiss cheese out of him?
Fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee-fee!
Come on, Straw Hat, you know you want...
Hey, it's him!
Wow, wonder what that room's used for.
What kind of monster fires off cannons inside someone else's ship?
At least he stopped running away.
You brandy!
I'll show you just to wait!
Aw, no way!
Come back and find me!
Doesn't he have any common decency?
Honestly, I've had enough foxy face transformation.
I got you now!
Who's that?
Dear me!
Are you ill?
Tell me where it turns and I'll fix it!
Is it your head?
Is that it?
Are you sick in the head?
Wait a sec!
Did you see someone else come through here?
Why, no!
I didn't see at all!
But never mind that!
You broke something, didn't you?
Your face?
I could have sworn I saw him go in there.
Hold on!
That weird lady!
She looked just like him!
I get it!
Hey!
You must be Foxy's sister!
You can't fool me!
Counter Foxy!
Oh!
Ah!
But that's it!
She lied to me so I wouldn't find her brother!
Is he even trying to fight anymore?
The kitchen!
A slice of the fish and what do you know?
You got some nice carpaccio.
Don't forget to go to the rotto.
Yes?
Have you seen some old fox dude with his head split in two
that looks really stupid and not cool?
You truly are heartless.
Hey, it's you!
And I was the woman in the doctor's office, too!
What? No way!
Slow, slow, beam!
Nine tails around!
I didn't just happen to lure you into the kitchen.
It's all part of the plan.
That is to say, I have a surprise waiting for you
after my punches take effect.
Do you want to guess what it is?
It's nothing alive, at least.
That would be against the rules, after all.
Nonono
In case you haven't learned yet, once the effect of my slow-slow beam wears off, all
those punches are going to hit you at once. That's it. Keep going. You're only a couple
of feet away from your final resting place. And that's 30 seconds.
Oh, where'd he run off to now? Turn around! I'm right here!
What kind of costume is that? It's not a costume, it's a pilot's uniform.
And this is my robot! A boxing masterpiece, corrected and perfected through countless trials.
Let me introduce you to the Gorilla Puncha 13!
The only gorilla I see on it is you! And it's you! And it's you! And it's you! And it's you!
All right! We'll have to change that!
Wait! Shut up! Jeez, you're so rude! Gorilla Puncha 13, let's finish him!
How do you get that crazy thing to move anyway?
It's a CK! Sure are sweating a lot!
You're seeing things!
If you think you can dodge, then be my guest! But be warned, I won't make it easy for you! Slow-slow beam! Ha!
What the heck are you aiming at?
Take a look behind you!
Huh? Is someone there? It's a mirror!
Yes! And the mirrors reflect slow-mo bottles! I got you!
I've got you!
Oh, what's the matter?
Can't take the heat?
Did I forget to mention these gloves burn like fire?
Cause they do!
Not even sea kings can stand a beating from this thing!
Mirror racket!
That's right, dance for me!
It's a beam and punch combo!
I call this attack the Slowpoke Ball Demon Coach!
I get it.
So that's why his beams didn't work on that fish man.
This is a pain.
I gotta find a way to get in closer.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, you can't dodge forever.
What's it gonna be?
The beam or the machine?
Wait, that's it!
I never thought of that!
Oh no!
Pissed up!
Slow, slow beam!
Beam, beam, beam!
れて Get the book's golden heads!
Time marches on, but neither combatant has emerged as a winner in the final round of
this dainty-back fight. It's truly unusual for someone to last so long against Foxy in his own territory.
Even if they can't see him, the crowd cheers for our boss with all their hearts.
Luffy won't lose.
Well, that goes without saying. He's Luffy and he has an afro.
I'd say being Luffy should be more than enough, though the afro is nice.
Okay, you're gonna have to explain this afro thing to me. You're all acting like it powers him up, but that doesn't make any sense.
I think this is the longest combat round I've ever seen. The guy is made of rubber, after all.
He's made of rubber and he has an afro.
Really? Am I the only one who doesn't get this?
I'm not scared, because no matter what, I know Luffy's gonna win this and get us back.
Of course. He does have that afro and all.
You too?
What's this? It looks like something is happening on the deck.
Who has the upper hand? Or perhaps the battle is ended with a bang and only one fighter remains.
No, wait. I see two people.
But only one of them is standing, and it's...
Yes! Power Boss!
Meanwhile, it looks like Straw Hat has been burned to a crisp. He must have taken some seriously hot punches.
Luffy!
No way.
It takes more than punches to burn someone like that. What gives?
Luffy!
Wait, look.
He's up!
I can't stall on! Straw Hat is up!
It seemed like he was down for the count, but the fight goes on!
You're persistent. I'll give you that much, rubber boy.
It's afro-power! What else could it be?
Finish him, boss!
Take this!
That's the slow, slow-beam sword!
As I'm sure you can probably tell, I've restrained your arms and legs.
Good luck with that.
Good luck!
You're gonna need it.
Good luck with that.
Megaton Nine Tails rush!
Rush!
That's 30 seconds.
He's down for sure this time!
No!
Not yet!
Come on!
He's up!
He's really up!
That's nuts!
Who is this guy?
They shouldn't have let him have that afro!
Nobody can stop him now!
Stubborn brat!
Take this!
Another slash the beam!
Megaton Nine Tails rush!
That beam is for cheaters!
Try fighting like a man for once!
Sit down!
No!
This looks like the end!
Oh!
Please, guys!
Take this!
Look, look!
You got it!
Move, move, back!
It's just a garnered, in and off, and off.
It's for many.
What is a ring?
Megaton Ninetales rush!
That beam is for cheaters! Try fighting like a man for once!
Sit down.
No! This looks like the end!
Dealing the punches ain't so easy either, kid.
He's beating Lupi to death out there!
He's giving up again?
He's tough!
Lupi?
I won't let you take a single member of my crew, even if it kills me!
He's on his feet!
Straw Hat Luffy refuses to give in!
Spongebob bounce, madness.
YEPC
We'll see you next time.
On the next One Piece, Epic Heated Combat,
the fateful final conclusion,
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!